[Intro]
[Verse 1]
The Lord is my shepherd,
and I shall want nothing.
In a place of green grass
there he has made me dwell.
He has nourished me
by the water of rest.
[Verse 2]
He has restored my soul,
he has guided me
in the paths of righteousness
for his name's sake.
[Chorus]
Even if I should walk
in the shadow of death,
I will fear no evil,
for you are with me.
Your rod and your staff,
they have comforted me.
I will fear no evil.
[Verse 3]
You have prepared a table before me
in the presence of those who afflict me.
You have anointed my head with oil,
and your cup cheers me like the best wine.
[Chorus]
Even if I should walk
in the shadow of death,
I will fear no evil,
for you are with me.
Your rod and your staff,
they have comforted me.
I will fear no evil.
[Bridge]
Your mercy shall follow me
all the days of my life.
[Final Chorus]
I will fear no evil,
for you are with me.
The Lord is my shepherd,
and I shall want nothing.
[Outro]
And I shall dwell in the house of the Lord
for a very long time.
The Lord is my shepherd.
[End]